Episode 24
第 24 集
Public security, the skill of making tea...
公安、泡茶技艺……
It's gotten better recently.
最近好多了。
As long as dad likes it.
只要爸爸喜欢就好。
I heard that you sold all my stores.
我听说你卖掉了我所有的商店。
It's yours. You are free...
是你的。 你自由了...
Use it however you like.
您可以随心所欲地使用它。
But if you need money...
但如果你需要钱...
You can tell your dad
你可以告诉你爸爸
My brother put up a warning sign...
我哥哥立了一个警告牌...
At our village shrine...
在我们村的神社...
Are you organized?
你有组织吗？
approximately.
大约。
Dad said...
爸爸说...
Dad will take me and mom...
爸爸会带我和妈妈...
A vacation to unwind.
一个放松的假期。
Are you still willing to do that?
你还愿意这样做吗？
Yes, but let's wait a little longer.
是的，但是 让我们再等一会儿。
Your brother's murderer...
杀害你兄弟的凶手...
No arrests have been made yet.
目前尚未逮捕任何人。
Dad will feel at ease...
爸爸就会安心...
After this incident.
这件事发生之后。
Please submit this inquiry...
请提交此询问...
To Magistrate Don.
致唐法官。
That's his job...
那是他的工作...
So he is more skilled than his father.
所以他的技术比他的父亲还要高。
why?
为什么？
You want to go quickly, Qian?
钱，你想快点走吗？
This yellow blue is boring.
这个黄蓝色很无聊。
I don't want to stay here for long.
我不想在这里呆太久。
This is the way.
就是这样。
Go for a walk outside the city with your mom.
和妈妈一起去城外散步。
I'll look for you in a few days.
过几天我去找你。
But I'd rather go...
但我宁愿去...
with mom and dad
和爸爸妈妈
Do you know where to go?
你知道去哪里吗？
I want to go to a small town..
我想去一个小镇..
South of the Yangtze River.
长江以南。
I heard there are a lot of bridges and rivers ...
听说那里有很多桥梁和河流 ......
So it's a perfect place to relax .
所以这是一个完美的放松场所 。
great.
伟大的。
I will spend a few days trying to get everything done .
我会花几天时间努力完成所有事情 。
After that, my father will resign.
在那之后，我父亲就会辞职。
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
of.
的。
Dad, I'll go first.
爸爸，我先走了。
great.
伟大的。
I forgot to ask him about Wu Shuomo .
我忘了问他吴硕模的事。
Forget it. I'll ask that person next time.
算了。 我下次再问那个人。
Kediaman Hua
华克迪亚
You are busy with official work today.
今天你正忙于正式工作。
I don't think he can make time now .
我想他现在抽不出时间了 。
What do you do when I ask you to come next time?
当我下次邀请你来的时候你会怎么做？
Because Mr. Jong is busy...
因为郑先生很忙...
I will wait here until he is released.
我会在这里等他被释放。
Teacher Hua, it's not a good idea to wait here .
华老师，在这里等 不太好。
What did you answer first?
你首先回答了什么？
I'll go to your house and let you know...
我会去你家 告诉你...
When Mr. Jong is free.
当Jong先生有空的时候。
I live in Hua Residence.
我住在华公馆。
I feel your guilt...
我感受到你的愧疚...
send me a message
给我发一条信息
It's okay to wait a while.
等一下就可以了。
Did he go there again?
他又去那里了吗？
Yes, it's full.
是的，已经满了。
That's strange. I think we were pretty close until not long ago.
真奇怪。 我认为直到不久前我们还很接近。
But these days, he keeps rejecting my invitations.
但这些天， 他一直拒绝我的邀请。
Di Mana Qi Ruxin?
迪玛纳齐如心？
Why haven't I seen him these days?
为什么我这几天没见到他？
I was traumatized after hearing that person's words...
听了那个人的话，我心里很受伤……
During the Mid-Autumn Festival.
中秋节期间。
So he was still resting in his room.
所以他还在自己的房间里休息。
let's go.
我们走吧。
It seems like it's been a while...
好像已经有一段时间了……
I have not visited your Majesty.
我还没有拜访过陛下。
But a lot of people come and go.
但来来去去的人很多。
When people see you standing here...
当人们看到你站在这里时...
that ...
那 ...
You have gone too far.
你已经走得太远了。
You know I won't allow it...
你知道我不会允许的...
People say it's you...
人们说是你...
So you wait at my door and don't want to leave.
所以你就在我家门口等着， 不愿离开。
You must stay away from me .
你必须远离我 。
Do you want to push me again?
你还想再推我一下吗？
Please let me know.
请告诉我。
What is the purpose of your visit today?
您今天来访的目的是什么？
You're not mad because you didn't come to me, right?
你并没有因为没有来找我而生气，对吗？
But you still seem angry at me...
但你似乎还在生我的气...
when i got here
当我到达这里时
Can you say you're coming for me?
你能说你是来找我的吗？
Came here today...
今天来到这里...
to ask for your help
寻求你的帮助
Sir, please relieve my guard.
先生，请解除我的戒备。
Because in the end , he's still the reason you came.
因为到最后 ，他仍然是你到来的原因。
In return...
作为回报...
I'll let me and Dad go...
我会让我和爸爸 走...
In the matter of my brother Hua Shen.
就我哥哥华神的事情而言。
You have full control.
您拥有完全的控制权。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
You should know what I mean.
你应该明白我的意思。
Your guard attacked first.
你的守卫首先进攻。
I don't want to let him go...
我不想让他走...
Just because you told me to do it?
就因为你告诉我这么做？
Hwa Yong-ju was wrong...
华勇柱错了……
But you don't need to kill him.
但你没必要杀他。
He suffered a lot as a child.
他小时候受过很多苦。
I understand if he feels good...
我理解他是否感觉良好...
It's hard to find a balance.
很难找到平衡点。
When he was young?
当他年轻的时候？
You believe everything he says.
你相信他所说的一切。
Mr. Lee, a wealthy merchant...
李先生是一位富商...
Killed many children.
杀死了很多孩子。
Her family did not expect Hua Rongzhou ...
她的家人没想到华容舟 ……
I will risk my life to atone for that sin.
我将冒着生命危险来赎罪。
Why did you force them to testify against him?
你为什么强迫他们出庭指证他？
He had been in jail for less than five days.
他入狱还不到 五天。
And coming to Jong Park...
来到Jong Park...
I ask for your help twice.
我两次请求你的帮助。
You said he was young.
你说他还年轻。
That is, at a young age...
也就是说，在年轻的时候...
Give him immunity from punishment?
让他免受惩罚？
Mr. Li should probably die...
李先生应该死了吧……
But Qi Rongzhou took more than one life.
但齐容舟夺走了不止一个人的生命。
What you mean is...
你的意思是...
Everyone must take responsibility ...
每个人都必须承担责任 ...
Because of their actions, right?
因为他们的行为，对吗？
Meng Libei sent people to kill me...
孟力北 派人来杀我……
But my brother died.
但我的兄弟死了。
If you value justice and equality...
如果你重视正义和平等......
As you said...
如你所说...
Why are you hiding this from me?
你为什么 要向我隐瞒这件事？
Why was there someone who missed it...
怎么还有人错过了……
When those people killed someone ...
当那些人杀了人的时候 ...
While others must atone for their crimes...
而其他人 必须为自己的罪行赎罪......
With their lives?
用他们的生命？
How are your parents?
你父母好吗？
Family crab...
家庭螃蟹...
I have no interest in the law.
我对法律没有兴趣。
The murder was carried out publicly.
谋杀 是公开进行的。
And they immediately...
他们立即...
It's rude to the Zhong family.
这对钟家来说太失礼了。
In fact, we caused your brother's death.
事实上，我们 导致了你兄弟的死亡。
So you think my younger brother is unhappy too...
所以你 以为我弟弟也不高兴……
Did he die because of the commotion?
他是因为骚乱而死的吗？
I am guilty.
我有罪。
I caused your brother's death.
我害死了你哥哥。
Did you know?
你可知道？
I became the target of a killer...
我成了杀手的目标……
And Hua Shen died to protect me...
而华神为了保护我而死……
With a knife attack?
用刀攻击？
I don't know
我不知道
yes. chaos...
是的。 混乱...
At the Mid-Autumn Festival banquet.
中秋宴会上。
Everyone ran away .
所有人都逃跑了 。
No one noticed anything different.
没有人注意到其他任何事情。
As one of the planners, you too...
作为策划者之一的你也...
Also, I don't know what happened.
另外，我也不知道发生了什么。
How would anyone else know?
其他人怎么会知道？
Prosecution investigation...
检方调查...
Controlled by bureaucracy.
受官僚机构控制。
It's faster if I do my own research.
如果我自己研究的话会更快。
In the end, I became the assassin's target...
结果我成了刺客的目标……
So I won't let that person go easily .
所以我不会轻易放过那个人 。
Miss Hua, you are very brave and smart.
华小姐， 你很勇敢，也很聪明。
I can't believe I'm writing this...
我不敢相信我正在写这个...
Do you want to make a deal with me now?
你现在想和我做一笔交易吗？
So you already know.
所以你已经知道了。
I can tell something...
我可以告诉一些事...
About the murder at the banquet.
关于宴会上的凶杀案。
During holidays...
假期期间...
Nothing is out of the ordinary...
没什么不寻常的...
About Hwangcheong's bodyguards.
关于黄清的保镖。
only...
仅有的...
progress.
进步。
A few days before the holidays...
距离放假还有几天...
Southern maid mung...
南方女仆蒙...
And to the north is Maid Qi.
北边是齐女。
Send people to deliver gifts.
派人 送礼物。
Why the Meng family?
为什么是孟家？
Meng has more than 20 aides…
孟有20多名助手……
He returns to the village with his wife and child .
他带着妻子和孩子 回到了村庄。
In the meantime, they also sent gifts and snacks...
与此同时，他们还送上了礼物和零食……
Chuseok prepared by her .
中秋节是她准备的 。
The person who received it was Master Maeng Du.
收到它的人是Maeng Du大师。
Until the third day after the holiday...
直到假期后的第三天...
20 people left the village...
20人离开了村庄...
And then head back south.
然后向南返回。
According to a spy from the Meng family...
据孟家探子透露……
Half of them are foreigners...
其中一半 是外国人...
I'm not even the one sending the gifts.
我什至不是送礼物的人。
Can we trust what the spy says?
我们能相信间谍说的话吗？
If you're not sure if you're a spy...
如果你不确定自己是否是间谍...
They won't report to us.
他们不会向我们报告。
In the end, it didn't make sense...
到最后，也没有意义……
Waiting too long...
等待太久了...
After delivery is completed.
交货完成后。
With all the recent events...
随着最近发生的所有事件...
Their strange behavior woke me up.
他们奇怪的行为 把我吵醒了。
There's nothing complicated.
没什么复杂的。
Why did it take me so long to find out?
为什么我花了这么长时间才发现？
The person who sent the gift...
送礼物的人...
Suspicious person from the Qi family ...
齐家的 可疑人……
So I spend a lot of time...
所以我花了很多时间...
Research the Qi family.
研究齐家。
Finally I found out...
最后我发现...
That man and Miss Chi...
那男人和池小姐……
There is a relationship.
有一种关系。
He had nothing to do with the murder.
他与谋杀案无关。
I knew from the beginning.
我从一开始就知道。
It was clear that Qi Ruxin was strange.
看得出来，齐如馨有些奇怪。
I never thought it would make me lose focus .
我从没想过这会让我失去注意力 。
Teacher, please forgive me!
请老师原谅！
You investigated the Meng family guards...
你调查了孟家的侍卫……
Who sent the gift?
礼物是谁送的？
I sent people south...
我派人去南方...
I'm trying to investigate secretly.
我正在尝试秘密调查。
Their findings...
他们的发现...
A security guard was killed by a robber .
一名保安被强盗杀害 。
Before you get to the store in the south.
在你到达南方的商店之前。
After the meng tide...
萌潮过后……
You may also know about this...
你可能还知道这个...
He also hires people...
他还雇人...
To get rid of the robbers .
去除掉强盗。
But that information came from a spy...
但这些信息 来自间谍……
And there are no witnesses.
而且没有目击者。
How dare you?
你怎么敢？
Are they really brave?
他们真的勇敢吗？
Many things...
很多东西...
It's not as easy as you think.
这并不像你想象的那么容易。
I'll keep it short.
我会长话短说。
Jangan Beoneo Hwayongju...
长安 Beoneo 花龙州...
I won't even open my mouth about Meng Yeobi...
我什至不会开口说孟也比的话……
my whole life
我的一生
Are security guards really important to you?
保安对你来说真的很重要吗？
That's not the problem.
那不是问题。
There aren't many people around me...
我身边的人并不多...
Treat me sincerely...
真诚地对待我...
So I am thankful for people who treat me well.
所以我很感谢那些对我好的人。
how about me
那我呢
Don't you know how I treat you?
你不知道我是怎样对待你的吗？
Why if I notice?
为什么我注意到了？
I made it clear from the beginning.
我从一开始就说清楚了。
Tuan is the head of the Zhong Family.
段是钟家的家主。
You have great responsibility for producing ...
您对生产...负有重大责任
Good for your health.
对你的健康有好处。
You always put business first...
你总是把生意放在第一位...
In a relationship with a woman.
与女人发生关系。
- I just... - You already know...
- 我只是... - 你已经知道了...
Meng Yifei is one of the people behind it.
孟一飞 就是其幕后黑手之一。
Behind the banquet murder...
宴会凶杀案的背后……
And how many times have you tried to stop me...
还有 多少次你试图阻止我......
meet him
见他
Aren’t you afraid I might find out?
你就不怕我发现吗？
The Meng family will be repaid.
孟家 必有报应。
I can guarantee that.
我可以保证。
But it's not time yet.
但现在还不是时候。
I know why.
我知道为什么。
The Meng family holds the operating rights...
孟氏家族 持有经营权...
Shops in the south.
南边的商店。
Forced coup…
强制政变…
It only weakens the power of the family...
只会削弱家族的力量……
And give others a chance too...
也给别人一个机会...
To take a chance.
抓住机会。
I know you have your reasons ...
我知道你有你的理由 ...
So that Meng Yifei and Qi Ruxin can stay...
这样才能让孟一飞和齐如馨留下来……
Di Taman species.
迪塔曼种。
Therefore you can't do anything to them.
因此你不能对他们做任何事。
I understand too...
我也明白...
You can't do whatever you want...
你不能为所欲为...
When you have power.
当你有权力的时候。
But it turns out...
但事实证明...
That doesn't mean I agree with your actions.
这并不意味着我同意你的行为。
Kian...
基安...
Even though you are a big shot...
虽然你是个大人物...
Justice cannot be guaranteed in all respects.
正义无法在所有方面得到保证。
Everyone has their own reasons.
每个人都有自己的理由。
If you release Huarongzhou...
如果放了华容舟……
I will convince my father to resign...
我会说服我父亲 辞职...
And we will return to the village.
我们将返回村庄。
We will no longer investigate Meng Lifei's affairs.
我们不会再调查孟丽菲的事情了。
you don't want to go
你不想去
I didn't think you wanted to go.
我没想到你想去。
Only I know what Meng Yifei did .
孟一飞做了什么只有我知道 。
If you don't believe me...
如果你不相信我...
Teacher, can you please shut my mouth...
老师， 请你闭嘴好吗？
And free the rest.
并释放其余的。
I have said this many times.
这句话我已经说过很多次了。
I never made any assumptions about you...
我 从来没有对你做过任何假设...
But you don't want to believe me
但你不想相信我
great.
伟大的。
then...
然后...
I won't waste any more time.
我不会再浪费时间了。
But know...
但知道...
I agree to all your requests...
我 同意你所有的要求...
Other than taking the guards with you...
除了带守卫一起...
I live outside Huangcheng!
我住在皇城外！
I won't allow it!
我不会允许的！
Teacher, what are you saying?
老师，您在说什么？
Perjanjian antara Qian Ying dan Mu Yunping
Perjanjian antara Qian Ying dan Mu Yunping
Evidence of my father's crime...
我父亲犯罪的证据...
What you have is just a copy.
你所拥有的只是一个副本。
You really think I don't know...
你真以为我不知道...
What did your father do?
你父亲做了什么？
You take good care of my jewelry.
你好好保管我的珠宝。
Do you remember the white jade bracelet...
你还记得那个白玉手镯吗？
Did he give it to me when I got married?
我结婚的时候他给我的吗？
Yes, I remember.
是的，我记得。
Please let me look for it.
请让我找找看。
I want to go to Taman Zhong tomorrow.
我明天想去Tamanzhong。
I have to send it back.
我得把它寄回去。
Okay, ma'am.
好的，女士。
Yixingxing is the owner.
宜兴兴是主人。
Why does the person seem to have changed?
为什么这个人 好像变了？
Maybe he will get better...
或许他会好起来……
After his wish came true.
当他的愿望实现后。
yes?
是的？
I think we should look into it.
我认为我们应该调查一下。
Choose a smart girl at Zhong Residence...
在忠宅选一个聪明的女孩...
And I set him aside.
我把他放在一边。
Have a nice day, madam. My name is Yixingxing.
祝您有美好的一天，女士。 我叫艺星星。
I told you earlier that I don't trust you.
我之前就说过我 不信任你。
I thought you didn't include it...
我还以为你没加进去呢...
The spy next to me.
我旁边的间谍。
I have to do this every time I go out...
我每次出门都必须这样做...
See you outside.
外面见。
i know...
我知道...
No matter how much I defend...
不管我如何 捍卫...
you won't trust me anymore
你不会再相信我了
But it's impossible for you and assistant Hua ...
但你和华助理这是不可能的 ……
You can leave Hwangcheong...
你可以离开黄清了...
No worries.
不用担心。
great.
伟大的。
You have complete control over us.
您对我们拥有完全的控制权。
Tracing a colleague is also a serious crime.
追踪同事 也是严重犯罪。
What do you mean, bring me death?
你什么意思，给我带来死亡？
Is it enough to atone for the sins of the father?
这足以弥补父亲的罪过吗？
You know what I'm thinking...
你知道我在想什么...
But you said that to make me angry.
但你 这么说是为了让我生气。
Teacher, do you know what I think?
老师，您知道我的想法吗？
Jong Si-woo.
钟时宇.
No, I have no idea what you're thinking .
不，我不知道你在想什么 。
It shows that you shouldn't make it...
这说明你不应该这么做...
Assistant Hua is in charge.
华助理负责。
So for what?
那么为了什么？
You said...
你说...
We will stop investigating the Meng Lifei incident...
我们将停止调查孟丽菲事件……
In exchange for the safety of the guards.
以换取守卫的安全。
I will allow...
我会允许...
Just reveal the truth...
只要揭露真相...
About Assistant Hua abusing his colleagues...
关于华助理 辱骂同事的事情……
To make sure he was safe.
为了确保他安全。
why me?
为什么是我？
Didn't you collect any evidence?
你没有收集证据吗？
You will find out later.
稍后你就会知道。
On the 5th of next month...
下个月5号...
I will call all the helpers in this city ...
我会召集这座城市里所有的帮助者 ……
To attend a banquet held at Zhong Park .
去参加在中公园举行的宴会 。
If you disclose this fact in front of those people...
如果你当着那些人的面透露这个事实……
I will free your family.
我会释放你的家人。
You think this is like a game.
你认为这就像一场游戏。
Should I hide my mistakes or reveal them...
我应该隐藏我的错误还是 揭露它们......
It's up to you.
由你决定。
Kian...
基安...
I will take your word for it.
我会相信你的话。
I’m going to pick up Hua Rongzhou now.
我现在就去接华容舟。
On the 5th of next month...
下个月5号...
I will do as you said.
我 会照你说的去做。
Pull out the insing...
拔出内裤...
please call that person again
请再给那个人打电话
I'm scared when I think of the results...
一想到结果我就害怕
If I protect that person
如果我保护那个人
Qian, believe it or not. Whatever I make...
钱，信不信由你。 无论我做什么...
I did it to make sure you were by my side.
我这样做是为了确保你在我身边。
Kian!
基安！
Let's go to jail first.
我们先去监狱吧。
Yes, it's full.
是的，已经满了。
Go to jail before you come back...
回来之前先去监狱吧...
Kediaman arose.
凯迪亚曼站了起来。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
Buy one.
买一个。
This basket is durable.
这个篮子很耐用。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
What is this?
这是什么？
Evolutionary powder, pain reliever.
进化粉，止痛药。
I was hurt because of you...
我因为你而受伤...
So you have to give me medicine .
所以你必须给我药 。
The light did not arrive.
光还没有到来。
follow me.
跟我来。
Get out.
出去。
I'm here to get you.
我是来接你的。
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
Miss, you don't look well.
小姐，你脸色不太好。
I like it.
我喜欢。
Miss cheating.
出轨小姐。
The lady is not good at cheating.
这位女士不擅长欺骗。
You don't have to say anything if you don't want to.
如果您不愿意，您不必说什么。
Aren't you smart?
你不聪明吗？
Huarongzhou...
华容洲...
Why does it look different than before?
为什么看起来和以前不一样了？
What's different?
有什么不同？
Guard Fire, this is your sword.
守卫火力，这是你的剑。
I brought it here for you.
我把它带到这里给你了。
Lady, I took a shower.
小姐，我洗澡了。
This is money and food.
这是金钱和食物。
You didn't even sign a contract...
你连合同都没签...
So I prepared all of this.
所以我准备了这一切。
Murder is still wrong.
谋杀仍然是错误的。
I did my best to save you ...
我已经竭尽全力救你了 ……
This time, starting with punishment.
这一次，从惩罚开始。
From now on, look for another job.
从现在开始，寻找另一份工作。
Miss said once...
小姐曾经说过...
They won't let me live alone ...
他们不会让我一个人住 ...
But now you want to leave me ?
但现在你想离开我 吗？
of.
的。
Shortcuts.
快捷方式。
We've known each other for a long time...
我们认识很久了...
So we will part ways amicably.
所以我们会友好地分道扬镳。
Please don't let me kick you out.
请不要让我把你踢出去。
There is no one in Hua Residence to compare with me.
华府无人能与我相比。
So if I want to stay here...
所以如果我想留在这里...
No one can kick me out.
没人能把我踢出去。
Say it again.
再说一遍。
Does this mean you can now disobey my orders?
这是否意味着你现在可以违抗我的命令了？
One time Miss said she would come with me.
有一次小姐 说她要跟我一起去。
At the prison entrance...
在监狱门口...
My aunt said she came to pick me up.
我姑姑 说她来接我了。
I believe every word you say.
我相信你说的每一句话。
Why did you break your promise?
你为何违背诺言？
Things are different now. I have...
现在情况不同了。 我有...
My previous actions were to protect myself.
我之前的举动 都是为了保护自己。
I have never intentionally caused trouble...
我从来没有故意惹麻烦……
Or hurt someone.
或者伤害某人。
If you're angry about my past mistakes ...
如果你对我过去的错误感到愤怒 ...
I promise...
我保证...
I won't do that again...
我不会再这样做了...
Unless instructed to do so.
除非指示这样做。
If you don't believe me...
如果你不相信我...
My right hand is going to be paralyzed...
我的右手快要瘫痪了
To show my resolve.
以表明我的决心。
Anyway, I learned martial arts...
反正 我是学武术的...
It is not for revenge or to harass the weak.
不是为了报复，也不是为了骚扰弱者。
Now I use it to protect you.
现在我 用它来保护你。
If you don't want me here...
如果你不想让我在这里...
My martial arts skills are useless.
我的武功毫无用处 。
You lied to me.
你骗了我。
When you leave Hwangcheong ...
当你离开黄清 ...
Lady, it's only me.
女士，只有我一个人。
So don't look for an excuse to kick me out.
所以别找借口把我赶出去。
I don't want you to be alone.
我不想让你孤单。
For me...
为我...
All this time, there was only you by my side.
一直以来，我的身边只有你。
when i see you
当我看见你时
I can't trust you if I entrust you with something important, right?
如果我把重要的事情托付给你，我就不能信任你，对吗？
I will improve myself.
我会提高自己。
OK. I won't kick you out.
好的。 我不会把你踢出去。
Thank you, ma’am.
谢谢你，女士。
You may go now.
你现在可以走了。
Yes, it's full.
是的，已经满了。
That person is just as stubborn as me...
那个人和我一样固执......
In my past life
在我的前世
But the best thing for him is to leave here.
但对他来说最好的事情 就是离开这里。
Forget it I'll think of another way.
算了 我会想别的办法。
Have you seen YixingSing?
你看过艺兴Sing吗？
I didn't see him today.
我今天没有见到他。
I told him to go.
我告诉他走吧。
What did he do?
他做了什么？
It's the same reason I told Cuizhu to leave.
这和我叫翠竹离开的理由是一样的。
It seems we can't trust the maid...
看来我们不能相信女仆……
In our area.
在我们地区。
Miss, don't worry.
小姐，别担心。
I won't betray you.
我不会背叛你。
Unable to.
无法。
Nanfeng may come looking for you.
南风可能会来找你。
Why didn't you run when your face was red?
脸红了怎么不跑？
Say whatever you want.
你想说什么就说什么吧。
I'm used to it.
我习惯了。
Another fun craft is missing.
另一种有趣的工艺缺失了。
Find someone to send to...
找人发给...
What are you waiting for? fast.
你在等什么？ 快速地。
- Don't be late. - Miss, that person...
- 别迟到了。 ——小姐，那个人……
sun. fast.
太阳。 快速地。
go away.
离开。
Bring a bottle of special black wine ...
带上一瓶特制的黑葡萄酒 ......
And come with me.
跟我来吧。
Okay, ma'am.
好的，女士。
Qubur Huashen
去布尔化神
This is a special black wine. My sister's favorite.
这是一种特殊的黑葡萄酒。 我姐姐的最爱。
Does it smell good, Shen?
沉，味道好闻吗？
I'm not good at drinking alcohol...
我不擅长喝酒...
So let's drink later.
那么我们稍后再喝吧。
Let me tell you what I want to say first.
我先告诉你我想说的话。
Please forgive me, brother.
请原谅我，兄弟。
I'm here to apologize again.
我又来道歉了。
I can not...
我不能...
File a lawsuit for your brother's death...
为你兄弟的死提起诉讼...
Even though I know the culprit.
尽管我知道罪魁祸首。
After all, there are North Korean defectors among you.
毕竟 你们当中也有脱北者。
We failed to do our duty.
我们没有尽到我们的职责。
When our master returns...
当我们的主人回来时...
We will offer our lives as a ransom.
我们将献上生命作为赎金。
I will suspend my sentence...
我会缓刑...
Until your master returns.
直到你的主人回来。
Leave the traitor to me...
把叛徒交给 我吧...
So that you can get your master back .
这样你就可以把你的主人找回来 。
We use several technologies...
我们使用多种技术...
Under interrogation.
正在接受审讯。
He cannot stand torture...
他受不了折磨……
and died
然后死了
Do you want your master back or not?
你到底想不想让你的主人回来？
Please forgive me, Mrs. Mu.
请穆太太原谅。
We can't...
我们不能...
Please hand over the North Korean defector.
请交出脱北者。
why?
为什么？
Our master is planning to kidnap the banquet...
我们的主人 正计划绑架宴会……
because I missed you
因为我想念你
It has to be a secret plan.
这一定是一个秘密计划。
We do it under the guise of Family Ge...
我们打着 Family Ge 的幌子做这件事...
So that no one doubts us .
这样就没有人怀疑我们了 。
Who would have thought that someone would die?
谁会想到有人会死？
If only people knew about Wooyoung...
如果人们知道吴英的话就好了……
They are trying to kill Hua's helper son...
他们想要杀死华的帮手儿子……
Our lord will be considered the cause of this...
我们的主将被认为是造成这一切的原因......
Hostility between two families...
两个家庭之间的敌意……
Even though our master...
尽管我们的主人...
I want to kidnap Hua Chen...
我要绑架华晨...
And didn't kill anyone.
并且没有杀任何人。
The culprit was someone else.
罪魁祸首是别人。
But no one cares about the details.
但没有人 关心细节。
Our master is stubborn...
我们的主人很顽固...
And I insist that you take risks.
我坚持要求你承担风险。
We have no choice but to obey.
我们别无选择，只能服从。
If I get caught, I will commit suicide...
如果我被抓住了， 我会自杀……
And didn't say anything.
并且什么也没说。
However, there are North Korean defectors among us.
然而，我们当中也有脱北者。
He put our master's life in danger.
他使我们主人的生命处于危险之中。
No matter what happens, we can't give up on him...
不管发生什么， 我们都不能放弃他……
Provides information.
提供信息。
so...
所以...
You can just say...
你只能说...
Who caused Hua Shen's death?
华神之死到底是谁造成的？
great.
伟大的。
Do you think...
你认为...
Will Hua Qian be satisfied with this answer?
花千骨会对这个答案满意吗？
Could you please send him a letter first?
你能先给他写封信吗？
If the person is smart, he will understand.
如果这个人很聪明，他就会明白。
But if Hua Qian insists...
但如果华潜坚持的话……
I don't want to lose my master...
我不想失去我的主人...
We had to...
我们不得不...
Risking your life to save him.
冒着生命危险去救他。
Sir, Mu Yao has sent someone to deliver this letter.
先生， 这封信已经被慕瑶派人送来了。
Mu Yao wrote a letter to me...
慕瑶给我写了一封信……
And he said we all know the truth.
他说我们都 知道真相。
But we have to pretend not to know...
但我们必须假装不知道...
Because there is no evidence.
因为没有证据。
We found no evidence...
我们没有找到任何证据...
Because it's a murderer...
因为他是杀人犯...
Protect other killers.
保护其他杀手。
The only one who can perform ...
唯一能表演的人 ...
Pretend you don’t even know that.
假装你根本不知道这一点。
Brother, I can't do anything else.
兄弟，我 也无能为力。
This world is unfair.
这个世界是不公平的。
Relationships take precedence over the law.
关系优先于法律。
Blood debts are paid with blood...
血债是用血来偿还的……
It only applies to the lower classes of society.
它只适用于社会下层。
For some people, killing someone...
对于某些人来说， 杀人...
It's as easy as killing ants.
这就像杀死蚂蚁一样简单。
For some, seeking justice...
对于一些人来说， 寻求正义......
Like swimming upstream.
就像逆流而上一样。
sibling.
兄弟。
Please forgive.
请原谅。
I can't risk my life...
我不能冒生命危险...
To take down Meng Yifei.
拿下孟一飞。
Only I can write it...
只有我能写...
The information I heard...
我听到的信息...
In return...
作为回报...
for the benefit of
为了...的利益
Painter family.
画家世家。
Am I so mean?
我有那么刻薄吗？
After being reborn...
重生后...
I think...
我认为...
I'm far away from all of you...
我 离你们所有人都很远...
You can avoid repeating the same mistakes.
您可以避免重复同样的错误。
Now it seems like that...
现在看来是这样……
I was wrong.
我错了。
this...
这...
Secondly I was wrong.
其次我错了。
Do you know?
你知道吗？
I saw my brother die in front of me twice.
我 两次亲眼目睹我的兄弟死在我面前。
Don't worry, brother.
别担心，兄弟。
I'm going to make things difficult...
我会让事情变得困难...
That person.
那个人。
me...
我...
It's inherently evil.
它本质上是邪恶的。
How much.
多少。
sibling.
兄弟。
Lakaman Bonus
拉卡曼奖金
Aren't you smart?
你不聪明吗？
Be careful of injuries.
小心受伤。
welcome.
欢迎。